Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.VN www.Addic7ed.com
Hiiiiiiiiiiiii.
Well, howdy there, idiot farm girl.
I brought your squirrel some peanuts.
- Uh, squirrel?!
- Uh-huh.
That squirrel.
Now, now there, little sugar munch...
These here whiskers on my face
ain't nary no squirrel.
This here's a mushystash.
Here you go, little squirrel...
Hey! Hey now!
Quit shovin' yr peutte into my mustache!
Ya dumb veggie burger!!!
Hiiii!!!
Looky...
that's my brother, Clem.
- Nice to meetcha there, Clem.
- Ahhh!! Squirrel!!!
- Ouches!
Ya slang-sheeted my mustache!!!
- Ow!
Where's your respect for cowboys?!
That's all we have.
I was supposed to come up with an ending.
- But she didn't.
- I did not.
And this has been...
... iCarly!
Guest starring meeeee!
- See ya next time.
- On the Web.
- Worldwide!
- Except for Yerba.
Where they have no freedom.
- Lighten up, Yerba!
- C'mon!!!
Squirrel!
And we're clear.
- Yay!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
Whoo!
Good job, brothah.
Yep. Okay, I'm gonna go soak
my feet in milk.
- All right.
- Sounds good.
- So weird.
- Bye.
Hey, hey...Check out
the email we all got.
- Who from?
- "Olympia Municipal Courthouse."
"To Carly Shay, "samantha
Puckett, "fredward Benson,
Oh my God, it says:
"Nora Dershlit is scheduled "for
a parole hearing next week..."
Nora who trapped us in her basement?
That luna-chick?
- Uh-huh.
"...And, as the victims
of her crime,
"you may attend and express your opinions
"as to whether or not miss Dershlit
should be kept in prison... or released."
How can they even think
about letting her out?!
Do you have any pudding cups?
Just one, and I already promised Freddie
he could have it after the show.
Ahhhh!
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.VN www.Addic7ed.com
In 5, 4, 3, 2...
♪ I know, you see ♪
♪ somehow the world will change for me ♪
♪ and be so wonderful ♪
♪ live life, breathe air ♪
♪ I know somehow we're gonna get there ♪
♪ and feel so wonderful ♪
♪ it's all for real ♪
♪ I'm telling you just how I feel ♪
♪ so wake up the members of my nation ♪
♪ it's your time to be ♪
♪ there's no chance unless you take one ♪
♪ and it's time to see ♪
♪ the brighter side of every situation ♪
♪ some things are meant to be ♪
♪ so give me your best ♪
♪ and leave the rest to me ♪
♪ leave it all to me ♪
♪ just leave it all to me ♪
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.VN www.Addic7ed.com
Oh, yeah.
Oh. Oh.
Sam, Sam...
Too late,
I already put my tongue in the pudding cup.
I don't care about the pudding cup!
I did!
We all have to go to Olympia next week
and speak at Nora's parole hearing!
- For what?
- For wh... ?!
For to make sure that they keep
that crazy girl in prison!
- Maybe they should let her go.
- What?! Why?!
Look, I've been in prison.
It is not fun in there.
And maybe when Nora trapped us,
she was, like, depressed or something.
Yeah well, I was bummed when I
didn't get asked to junior prom,
but did I lure the cast of full house
into my basement and torture Uncle Jesse?
Man, I'm so dang sick of this!
What are you doing?!
Puttin' on a suit so I can go home!
Dude, you don't need to keep pretending
to be mister perfect for Freddie's mom.
- Yeah he does!
- See?!
- If my mom sees
how T-Bo really is,
she's never gonna let him stay
in our house.
No offense.
Oh, I'm not offended.
I feel all warm inside knowing your mom
would be disgusted if she knew the real me.
It's not that.
It's...Yeah it's that.
That's nice.
Let's all just pretend
that T-Bo doesn't have feelings.
- Hey Teebs, wanna see what I got?
- Not really!
Gibbehhh.
- Hallo.
- Hey, baloney.
- Where have you been?
- The mall.
With my head up inside somethin'
for almost two hours.
Please say it was a horse.
Nope.
But it was inside
this really cool machine...
That made this!
- Holy...
- Cabeza!
- Noooooo.
- Whoa.
It's an exact replica of my own head!
- What does it do?
- Blow minds.
Look awesome.
- Wasn't it expensive?
- Oh yeah.
- Where'd ya get the money?
- From that diaper commercial I did.
- Oh yeah.
- Ahh.
- Are your feet in milk?
- Yep.
I love that.
Hey, did you see the email
we got about freaky Nora?
Yeah. That's nice that
they're lettin' her out.
What?! What is the
matter with everyone?!
That girl kidnapped us
and beat the Fudge outta you!
Look, I'm forgiving.
And I like chinese food.
That's who I am.
That's who we are.
Well, sorry. But we're all
going to that parole hearing
and we're all gonna tell the judge
that Nora needs to be kept in prison.
Mmmmmm.
I love that new head smell.
Hey...How come you have
dog toothpaste in your bathroom?
I heard that dogs' mouths
are cleaner than human's...
So I got to thinkin'...
Maybe it's their toothpaste.
You do not brush your teeth
with dog toothpaste.
I do too!
And watch... tickle my tummy.
Arrr!
So how long 'til you
have to be back at work?
- About forty-five.
Oh. Well, maybe we should skip the
spaghetti tacos and get right to dessert.
Ohhh, what are you serving?
- Lips and fresh berries.
- I don't see any berries.
There are no berries.
Hey!
- Hey T-Bohhh,
how ya doin'? Get out.
- I need to use your shower.
- Why can't you shower at your place?
'Cuz Mrs. Benson
don't "believe" in hot water.
So all they have is a warm water heater.
- So take a warm shower.
- No!
Warm water don't melt T-Bo dirt.
- That a spaghetti taco?
- Yeah, it is - wait - no...
I'm kind of in the middle
of a lunch date with Cassie.
I don't know Cassie.
- Where ya goin'?!
- To your shower!
But I don't want you...
I'm upset!
Oh. It's okaaaaay.
I like your face.
Dog toothpaste?!
Washington state women's penitentiary.
All right...
Nora Dershlit... you may speak
on your own behalf.
Thank you, judge Moil.
The word "sorry" doesn't even begin
to express how terrible I feel for...
For what I did to the iCarlys...
People who I wanted only to respect me...
To like me...
And to accept me as a person,
and a chicken lover.
I'm not worthy of freedom.
I deserve to rot in my cell.
It's not a joyful life, but not much
worse than the life I used to have.
At least now I'm surrounded
by other prisoners.
So... in a way,
I finally have friends.
Oh, I'm sorry mom and dad.
The victims
will now have a chance to speak.
Thank you judge.
Look, Nora...
What you did was...
Without...
- Without consequences...
- Ehhnn.
- ...A person never learns to...
- Hhhnn.
Oh, just let her go!
Let her go!!!
It's okay. Shut up. Shut up.
Wanna smell my head?
Washington state women's penitentiary.
Nora Dershlit...
Trapping the stars of a Web show in
your basement is a serious crime.
But since your victims...
- What is that?
- Oh. This is an exact replica of my head.
Is it blowin' your mind?
Yes.
Nora... these nice iCarly kids have
forgiven you for what you did.
And since your life up to this
point has been truly pathetic...
This court takes pity on you.
Nora Dershlit is hereby granted parole,
to be immediately released
to the custody of her parents.
- Oh, thank goodness!
- Bailiff, remove her handcuffs.
- Aw, you guyyyyssss...
- Aw.
Aw. I don't know what to say.
After what I did to you iCarlys
on my 16th birthday,
you came all the way here today
and helped me regain my freedom.
Ah, you don't have to thank us.
We're just happy
you're a better person now.
Oh, I am!
I know I am!
C'mon Nora...
we've got a surprise
Norwegian Supper
waiting for you back at home.
- Wow, truly?!
- Yes baby.
And we've invited
all your classmates from school.
And they're all coming?!
- No.
- None of them are.
Oh. Well...Carly, Sam, Freddie,
Gibby, Gibby's head...
Would you all please come?
- Oh, we gotta go back to Seattle.
- I got a pilates class.
Well, that's okay. I guess it'll
just be me, my mom, and my dad.
Sorry. I can't make it, baby.
- Why not?
- I wanna go camping alone tonight.
Oh. I guess it'll just be
supper for the two of us then.
Okaaay, we'll come
to your Norwegian Supper.
You will?!
All of you will?!
- Yeeaaahhh.
- Whatever.
Oh yay!
Yay for days!
Hey, uh...
Anybody here see my taser?
- Sam...
Oh, was this your taser?
- Spencer?
- Hang on, I'm just getting my pants ready!
- Okay! Heyyyyy Cassie.
- Heyyyy.
- Boo!
- Oh yeah! You got the new zombie death squad game!
- Uh-huh! And all the weapons.
- Aw. You genius!
C'mon, let's pop this sucker in
and hit play!
Easy boy...
What's the rush? Hmm?
I can't take it, I can't
take it, I can not take it!
- Dude...
- You know what's really irritating?!
- Could it be you?
- No!
Mrs. Benson's makin' me play
Mahjong with her!
Y'all ever play Mahjong?
- Uh, no.
- Not really, no.
Well it's a terrible game!
What is your name again?
You are fine.
- Terrance... Terrance...
- Aw, here it comes...
- Terrance, are you in here?
- Yes, Mrs. Benson.
I was just telling everyone about
our stimulating game of Mahjong.
Well, I'm afraid we're going
to have to play later.
Oh no.
Aw, you have to leave?
That's too bad byeeeee.
I'm sorry, but my sister
Susan used some new shampoo
that she was allergic to and now her
scalp is covered with blisters.
I've got to get over there
with a wire brush.
Oh, those blisters
aren't gonna pop themselves,
and we've got zombies to murder.
Oh look there's a door,
you can exit through that one.
Please keep an eye
on our apartment tonight...
I'm gonna sleep over at Susan's house.
No worries Mrs. Benson.
Would it be okay if I vacuumed?
Oh Terrance, you always know
the right thing to say.
Drive safely!
Make sure you lock your...
I'd like to take a wire brush to her.
My stupid tv broke again.
Oh, you got the new zombie
death squad game?!
- Uh-huh.
Let's take this chiz across the
hall to my place, we'll play there!
C'mon, let's go!
- Wait...
- What?
Why don't we let him play over there?...
... And you and I
could play over here, Hmm?
How?! The game's over there!
Oh, I'm home!
This is where I belong!
Back in the bosom of my youth!
- Bosom.
- I know.
Maurice!!!
Oh, Maurice, I missed you so much.
Gimme some beak.
This place brings back the memories, huh?
Yep.
Hey Nora... remember
when your clown had an aneurysm?
Or should I say 'clown-eurysm'?
Yes.
Poor cramps.
Okay kids, we don't need to
talk about that terrible day...
Not when we have this beautiful
buffet of Norwegian foods.
Yeah... what exactly
are "norwegian" foods?
- Well, we have... lutefisk...
- Lutefisk?
It's dried cod fish soaked in a
lye solution for several days...
That's nauseating.
Nauseatingly delicious.
And then we have warm tongue with flan...
Ooo, and what about dessert...
Beef cookies and cream!
Okay, even I can't eat this chiz.
Hey, there's no way we're gonna make
the last train back to Seattle.
I'll just text Spencer
and tell him to come pick us up.
Hey... pick us up from...
Nora's at... about 9:00.
- Try this monkfish liver.
- Or... sooner.
Yeah. Take that, zombie!
Yeah! He took it!
- Ah! Where'd my zombie go?
- It's behind ya!!!
- Swing it!!!
- Uh-huh.
Watch out!!!
Ahhh, zombie teenagers!!!
I'm back...
I forgot my wire br...
Mrs. Benson!
Ryan Seacrest!
Oh.
- I'mma have to call you right back.
- It's not a phone.
Good evening.
Terrance! You had a party in my
home without my permission?!
- Uhhh...
- And what are you wearing?!
Well, you see...
All right, you want the truth?!
- Yes! Right now!
- Y... I...
Okay!
Nobody calls me Terrance!
I am T-Bo! T! Bo!
I'm not fancy!
I don't talk like this.
I sling smoothies, I put food on
sticks, and I like a lotta women!
- You lied to me!
- So much!
- Why?!
- So you'd rent me a room!
Now... this is the real me!
You can either accept me as I
am, or just tell me to get out.
Get out.
And take your big axe with you!
- And what kinda cream is this?
- It's made from pig's milk.
- I'm done.
- I'm full.
That's enough a'that.
I love pig's milk.
I love it right from the pig.
- Oh, that must be Spencer.
- I'll fetch him.
Hi, I'm Spencer Shay.
I know we just met,
but I drank a double big chug
on the way up here,
and if I don't hit a bathroom
in the next 30 seconds...
Of course.
Mother? Would you please
show Spencer to our best toilet?
Certainly.
We just got a new one downstairs.
It's comfort height.
Oh. Any toilet will be fine.
Come with me.
Well, Nora...
Thanks so much for the awesome
Norwegian Supper.
Yeah, I guess I've had worse dinners.
Oh, you're all so welcome.
Love the beef cookies.
And congrats on being released from prison.
Thank you.
Okay...
I guess this is goodbye.
Ohhhhhh...
No, it's not.
Yeah, we really gotta get back.
Yeeeaaah...
but you're not gonna.
Uh, what are you talkin' about?
You children are going to
be here for quite a while.
Yes. You will.
I know you will.
- It's locked.
- Move.
- Unlock it, Nora.
- No.
The windows.
I don't think you'll be able
to get them open either.
I know how to get a window open.
- All the windows have been
replaced with maxi-glass.
They're quite unbreakable.
Yeah?
Well I don't think your faces
are made outta maxi-glass.
Get 'em, Sam.
Wow Carly. I thought
you cared about your brother.
Sam wait!!!
What are you talking about?
My new favorite television program.
Jake and the fat man?
No. "Wheel... of...
Carly!!
"- ...Spencer."
Help! Help meeee!
I'm on a wheeeeel!
- Spencer, where are you?!
- He's in the basement!
That's right.
Spencer!
I'm afraid the door to the
basement is quite locked.
And if Sam or any of you
try to harm me or my mother,
this is what will happen...
- Whoa wait... what -
what's happening...
I'm turning...
I'm rotating...
Aah!
I'm turning!
And I still have to peeeeeeeeeeeee!!!
Aah!
Yaaaaaahhhhhhhh!!!
Spencer!
Spencer...!!!
Silly Carly...
he can't hear you.
- He's in the basement.
- Would ya stop that wheel?!
- Oh, I'd be glad to.
- Aah!
Oh.
Ohhh... it stopped spinning.
Great.
Now I can puke.
No need to watch that.
Don't turn it off!
It was just gettin' good!
Nora... you're a nut case!
The proper term is "disturbed,
lonely sociopath."
Look dude, we're the ones
who got you outta jail.
True. But first, you tainted the
memory of my 16th birthday party.
So now, we're going to undo the taint.
Mother, please fetch our party guests.
- B-r-b.
You're the one who ruined the
memory of your own birthday party!
Everything woulda been cool if you'd
just let us go home afterwards!
Instead of you and your stupid
chicken locking us in your basement!
You will never besmirch
the name of my chicken!
You apologize to Maurice right now!
Ah sniff it, Nora.
I will not sniff it...
But I will give Carly's brother the spins!
Oh, no.
I'm moving again...
Why is it turning?
What's happeniiiinnnnngggg?!
- Aah!
- Just apologize to the chicken!!!
I'm so very dizzy!
I'm sorry I b'smeared your
name by calling you stupid!
And that I've eaten
thousands of your relatives.
Thank you, Sam.
Now let's all wear party hats!
There's some right over there.
- We're not wearing party hats!
- Put on the hats!!!
Why don't we put on the hats then?
Wait a second...
Why you guys starin' at me?
- You said, "wait a second."
- Oh yeah.
There's four of us, and one of Nora.
So let's just take that remote
away from her.
Ooo, bad idea. See...
if any iCarlys make a sudden move,
I hit this special red button and Spencer spins
at top speed until his brain turns to goo.
- Goo?!
- Yes goo!
And you won't be able to stop it.
She's really thought this through.
Yes.
Prison gives a girl lots of time to think.
And to plan.
And to not shower.
Oh. Wow, okay,
getting weirder.
Uhhhh... what's goin' on?
Well, we can't have a birthday
party without a few more guests.
Now, I'll go pick out
an eight-track
so we can have some music
to, y'know, puff up your jams.
What is she talking about?
We're recreating
Nora's 16th birthday party.
Yes, and this time,
my party will be perfect.
And it will go on...
Forever and ever and ever.
♪ Dangerous ♪
♪ you don't wanna mess with us ♪
♪ you might think you're tough enough ♪
dance!!!
♪ Wait till I get my hands on you...Ooh ♪
♪ I'm gonna, gonna getcha ♪
no!
♪ I'm gonna getcha right now ♪
... so don't worry
about me, mom...
We're all safe at a hotel with Spencer.
Love, Freddie.
Send. There...
And that takes care
of all your cell phones.
You sick chick.
I think of myself more as...
"Disturbed."
Now... mother and I will go
fetch my birthday cake.
- Wait here children.
- Oh, silly mother...
They couldn't leave if they wanted to.
- Okay, what are we gonna do?
- I'll tell ya what we're gonna do.
Soon as those two freaks
walk back in here...
No!
No butter sock!
C'mon man!
You can't attack them as long as
Spencer's on that wheel in the basement
or else Nora's just gonna spin him again.
And anyway, that butter sock is gross.
I change the butter once a month.
Do you really?
No.
Man, there's no way
to get this window open.
Hey! I know how Santa claus
would get outta here.
Ooo, the chimney!
- Right.
- That's the one. Hurry.
No.
On a reindeer.
- Gibby.
- You idiot.
We thought you meant climbing
up the chimney.
That could also work.
Just stuff yourself up there
and go for help!
- Kay-kay.
- Wait wait wait!
The Dershlits'll notice he's gone.
Nooooo...
'Cuz "gibby's" gonna be
taking a nap on the couch.
Perfect!
Okay.
Sam, take the head off that dummy.
I don't know. I hate to damage
someone else's property.
- C'mon.
Hey, hey, be gentle with my head.
- Give me the blanket.
- I don't sleep on my side.
Shut up, gib! Shut up!
Cover his butt.
- There!
- Now let's get Gibby up that chimney!
- Go, go, go.
- Okay. Go. C'mon!
- Get your head in the thing!
- Hurry! Hurry! Faster! Faster!
- C'mon, hurry up. Faster!
- You're gonna come back. Hurry!
Just wiggle up the chimney
like a husky worm!
Shhh! Shhh! Here they come!
♪ Oh Nora's a jolly good person ♪
♪ oh Nora's a jolly good person ♪
♪ oh Nora's a jolly good perr-err-sonnnn... ♪
♪ now Freddie is gonna get kissed! ♪
what?
Those aren't the lyrics!
I don't wanna... aw, come on...
Here is your suitcase.
And some of your items.
But I don't wanna move out!
I don't give a bird's beak what you want!
Now take your things and leave!
But Freddie needs a male role model!
A man to look up to!
That's why this country has Tony Danza!
All right fine, you want
me to leave, I'll just...
- Ha! Look what I got!
- What's that?
My lease!
The lease that you and I both signed
that says your guest room here
is mine for a whole year!
This is a restraining order.
It says you must stay
at least one hundred yards away
from some girl named Porsha Sweet.
Ha, ha!
Here!
This is the lease!
And it says you can't kick me out!
Did you make a copy of this lease?
No.
I went to the copy place
but Porsha was there.
Dang!
You guys just stood there eating
cake while I was tampered with?!
It's really good cake.
Errrggg... ahhh...
Gibbehhh...
Yeeeaaahhh.
Fresh air, baby.
Now I gotta get to the cops.
And then crazy Nora is gonna find
herself back in prison where she...
Errrggg... ahhh... gibbehhh...
And I'm stuck.
- Did you enjoy your birthday cake?
- Oh, I did. I know I did.
Okay Nora, now that you've
eaten your birthday cake...
And my face.
- ...Can we go?
- Well, of course not.
- Gibby hasn't had any cake yet.
- Oh, uhhh... he's napping.
Yeah, he wasn't feeling too well so...
Still napping.
Nooooo, it's bad luck if ya
don't have some birthday cake.
Well, it's not really your birthday.
It is too!
Whether it's technically
my birthday or not,
we're all going to pretend
it's my actual birthday!!!
Do you understand?!
- Happy Birthday.
- Thanks, Carly.
Now, Gibby will eat some cake.
Wakey wakey, time for cakey...
All right!
Where is the real Gibby?!
Where is he?!
- He uhhh.
- Uhhh.
He's gotta be in this house somewhere.
Fine.
My mother and I will find him.
But this escape attempt
will not go unpunished.
Aw, are you gonna kiss me again?
Ooo, somebody's been missin' my kissin'.
No no no no no no.
I just meant...
Later!!! For now...
- No. Wait, Nora.
- No, no.
- Nora, stop, please.
- Argh.
No, c'mon... not again...
What did I do?
What did I dooooooo?!
- Gibby?! Show yourself?!
- Here, Gibby, Gibby, Gibby!
- C'mon, Gibby!
- Aah! I'm on a wheel!
- I'm stuck in a chimney!
- Wheel!
- Chimney!
- Gibby!
Aah!
- Here Gibby, Gibby, Gibby.
- Chimney!
- Sam... Sam... fried chicken.
- I want the leg, gimme the leg.
- What time is it?
- Morning.
I love fried chicken in the morning.
- There is no fried chicken!
- Then why'd you wake me?
'Cuz we're still trapped at Nora's!
Aw, look at Freddie.
What about him?
Boys are just so cute when they're asleep.
Ah! What happened?!
In five, four, three, two, what happened?!
We're still stuck at Nora's.
Aw, it's morning.
Where's Gibby with the police?!
I know, he shoulda been back here
with the cops a long time ago.
Okay, let's not freak out.
Gibby's probably with the police right now.
We just gotta stay cool
and have faith in Gibby.
- ...Gibbehh-gibbehh-gibbehh.
Behh-gibbehh-gibbehh-gibbehh...
- Ah, man - how long are we supposed
to stand here and wait for him?
Well, I'm not sure we have
lots of options as hostages!
Look, Gibby's gonna come back
with help and everything's gonna...
Ooo, are we talking about our friend Gibby?
Sorry, iCarlys...
But he's already been gone
for twelve hours.
So, it seems Gibby won't be
coming to your rescue this time.
Oh, boo-hoo! Boo-hoo! Waaah!
Waaah! Waaah!
- Heyyy. What's goin' on?
- It's Nora's dad!
We'll tell ya what's goin' on!
We've been held hostage here all
night by your psychotic daughter!
And your demented wife!
- And she's been spin-torturing
my brother!
- It's been a living nightmare!
- Well, that's terrible.
- Yeah!
- Duh!
Nora...
This is supposed to be a party.
A birthday party!
That will go on forever...
And ever...
- ...And ever and ever...
- ...And ever and ever
- and ever...
- Oh my God.
...And ever, and...
Hey! Hey, you kids!
Hey! Up here! Yeah, hi!
Uh, can I get a little help?
Hey, that's the dude from iCarly!
- Yeah, that's Gibby!
- Gibbehh!
Hey, Gibby!
Take off your shirt!
No!
I do that less frequently now.
Listen, I'm stuck and I can't move my arms,
I need you guys to call the cops!
- Let's throw balls at him!
- Yeah!
What?! Nooo!
Don't throw balls at me!
I'm completely vulnerable!
Why would you wanna throw...
Ha-ha!
Ya missed me, ya missed me
now ya gotta kiss...
Owwwww! This is how you
treat an Internet star?!
Stop it! Ahhhh!
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!!!
I'm so dizzy!
Carly!! Carly!!!
Will you stop spinning my brother?!
- No!
- Why?
I sang you Happy Birthday like you wanted!
- You were pitchy!
- Well!
- Woooo-aaaaaah! Ahhhhh! Carly!
- Run Gibby!
- Gibby?!
- He's still in the house!
- Check all the bedrooms!
- Gibby!
- Gibby, Gibby, Gibby!
You saw Gibby?!
No, I threw a glass thing
in there to buy us some time.
Time for what?
To figure out a way
to get us outta this nut hut!
Why hasn't your freakish mother
come looking for us by now?!
She thinks we're with Spencer
at a hotel so why would she...
The chip.
What chip?
The one my mom had surgically installed
in my head when I was a toddler.
If it stops transmitting, it triggers
an emergency distress gngnal on my mom's
tracking device and tells her my location!
Cool, then make it stop transmitting!
- Where's the off switch?!
- I don't know. It's in my head.
- Ah!
- Mrs. Benson, help us!!!
Shhhh! You want the Dershlits to hear you?!
Slapping my head isn't gonna
make the chip stop working!
Then what will make it stop working?!
And trigger the emergency signal?!
I... I guess it'd have to be
electrically shorted out somehow.
- Oh! The shock pen!
- Aw, the shock pen?
- Is that Spencer's?
- Yeah. I stole it! See?
Why'd you steal his shock pen?
'Cuz I like it, and I didn't have one.
Where's Gibby?!
Just don't look in your parent's shower!
The shower! Mother!
Father! Gibby may be showering!
Okay Benson,
I hope this thing is powerful
enough to blow that chip.
No no no no no!
Let Carly do it.
- Why?
- 'Cuz Carly cares about me.
At least she'll try to be gentle.
She won't just take that thing
and stick it...
Here, gimme that.
- What are you doin'?
- Just to be sure.
How did you get in here?
With my key...
that I'm returning.
Well put it on the table and go.
One sec... I gotta get my
shampoo outta the bathroom.
- No, just go buy some more.
- Unh-uh!
I bought that in Jamaica...
you can't even get it here.
Whatever... fine, go.
I don't know why you're bein' all sticky.
I moved out like ya told me to.
Just get your jamaican shamp...
- what's that?
- Oh my God, Freddie's in trouble!
- How do you know?
- I just know!!!
What if that crazy Nora girl
has done something again?!?!
All right all right, chill your wig.
- I've got to go help Freddie!
- Okay, I'll take you.
- I can drive myself!
- No, there'll be too much traffic.
We'll get there quicker on my motorcycle!
- O-okay! Where are you going?!
To get my seven dollar bottle
of Jamaica my hair so silky!
- C'mon Carly, you can do it!
- C'mon, get it down there.
Yeah. C'mon, Carly, do it.
C'mon. Yeah.
Your turn, Freddie.
Do it Freddie!
Get it on there good!
Who plays pin the tail
on the birthday girl?!
Yeah. And why is she
wearing the blindfold?!
Just pin the tail on my daughter's butt!
Yeah.
Okay!
This is outta control!
We've been here for fifteen
hours and we wanna leave!!!
- Open this door!!!
- No!
- We may never open that door!
- That's right!
Because my birthday party
shall go on forever and ever...
...And ever and ever
and ever and ever and ever and...
- Freddie!
- Mom!!!
- T-Bo!!!
- Chicken?!
- Freddie!
- Spin the brother!
Oh no.
I'm moving again!
Wooooaaaaahhhhhhhhhh!!!
No. No, stop it.
Give me the remote.
Stop it. Stop it. Stop. Stop.
Sam! Sam,
get me the remote from Nora!
No.
Spencer!
I can't get this stupid door open!
I got the key to that! Move!
Thanks!!!
- Spencer!!! Spencer!!!
- Carly... Carly, is that you?!
Yeah!
Oh, I'm gonna vomit so hard!
That's for breaking my doors!
- Ohhh, nobody spanks T-Bo!
Mother!
Careful Sam, those are sharp!
So are these!
You girls want a little taste
of a fencin' Benson?
- Is it stopped?
- Yeah.
Have I stopped spinning?
Yeah mom! Get her!
You made a hamburger?!
Your mom's got this.
I put his robe on him backwards.
Okay...
I'm tired a'these Dershlits.
Tired of us?
What does that me...
Wait wait wait I'm allergic to...
I warn you, Sam Puckett, you better...
- I... I am so nauseous!
- It's okay, you're okay.
I might puke on your shoulder.
I'm sorry, I puked on your shoulder.
It's okay, just never talk about it.
Nice work, mom.
You too, Terrance.
Aw, give it up man...
Your mom busted me.
And she kicked me out.
Aw, you kicked him out?
Yes, but I'm kicking you right back in.
One more time???
- Terrance... T-Bo...
You helped save my Freddie...
So you may keep your room in our house.
For four hundred dollars a month.
- Awww, Mrs. Benson...
- Don't touch us!!!
Wh... what's...
What's happening...?
You wanna know what's happening, Nora?
You and your freak parents
are going to prison.
- Forever and...
- ...Ever and ever and ever
- and ever?
- Yes.
And ever and ever and ever and ever...
Kids can help you with it,
everybody has been doing this.
And again, you bake it instead of frying
so that you're saving tons of fat...
Hey dad!
No, it's almost two in the morning here.
How'd you know?
It was on the news?!
No... no, no, we're all fine.
Yeah, they took the girl and her parents
to jail so, y'know, happy ending.
I promise.
Carly's up in her bed,
safe, and sound asleep.
Gibby!!!
Hey?! Anyone?!
I'm still heeeeere!!!
Gibbehhh...
Aw, more balls?!
Nah...Oh...Oh...
Gibby.
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.VN www.Addic7ed.com
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0